{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Lightning Rod Companies","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/39779/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":39779,"taskName":"Lightning Protection - Install or Repair","taskDescription":"Install Lightning Protection Systems","xmTaskDescriptor":"Lightning Rod Companies","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":152,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Lightning cable antennas rod detector","textMessagingName":"Lightning Protect","rolloverLongDesc":"This person installs metal devices high up on tall trees, buildings \u0026 other structures \u0026 connects those lightning attracting devices to the ground with stout cabling in order to safely channel the electricity so it does not burn or destroy the tree or structure.","rolloverShortDesc":"Lightning rods \u0026 cables in trees \u0026 structures.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install Lightning Protection Systems.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Lightning Rod Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Lightning Protection","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":25,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Lightning Protection Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Lightning Protection - Install or Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Lightning Protection Project","urlName":"Lightning-Protection-Install-or-Repair","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Lightning Rod Installers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"Lightning,cable,antennas,rod,detector,roof,metal,Protection","emcCategoryOid":-12026,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":311,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/39779/":{"taskOID":39779,"originalTaskOID":39779,"setID":311,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4006,"questionDisplayText":"Describe area around home","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes the immediate area of your home?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6631,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Urban","answerDisplayText":"Urban","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3981,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Mountains","answerDisplayText":"Mountains","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2509,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Flat land","answerDisplayText":"Flat land","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6491,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Trees","answerDisplayText":"Trees","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6842,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Water","answerDisplayText":"Water","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4005,"questionDisplayText":"Square footage of house","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the square footage of your home?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":200783,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 1,000 Square Feet","answerDisplayText":"Less than 1,000 Square Feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200822,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"1000 - 2000 Sq ft","answerDisplayText":"1000 - 2000 Sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200821,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"2000 - 3000 Sq ft","answerDisplayText":"2000 - 3000 Sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200823,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 3000 Sq ft","answerDisplayText":"More than 3000 Sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4007,"questionDisplayText":"Number of Stories","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many stories is your home?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10011,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10012,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2","answerDisplayText":"2","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10013,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"3","answerDisplayText":"3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":473,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"4 or more","answerDisplayText":"4 or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4006,"questionDisplayText":"Describe area around home","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes the immediate area of your home?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6631,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Urban","answerDisplayText":"Urban","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3981,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Mountains","answerDisplayText":"Mountains","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2509,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Flat land","answerDisplayText":"Flat land","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6491,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Trees","answerDisplayText":"Trees","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6842,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Water","answerDisplayText":"Water","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6631,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Urban","answerDisplayText":"Urban","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3981,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Mountains","answerDisplayText":"Mountains","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2509,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Flat land","answerDisplayText":"Flat land","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6491,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Trees","answerDisplayText":"Trees","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6842,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Water","answerDisplayText":"Water","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4005,"questionDisplayText":"Square footage of house","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the square footage of your home?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":200783,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 1,000 Square Feet","answerDisplayText":"Less than 1,000 Square Feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200822,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"1000 - 2000 Sq ft","answerDisplayText":"1000 - 2000 Sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200821,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"2000 - 3000 Sq ft","answerDisplayText":"2000 - 3000 Sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200823,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 3000 Sq ft","answerDisplayText":"More than 3000 Sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":200783,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 1,000 Square Feet","answerDisplayText":"Less than 1,000 Square Feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200822,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"1000 - 2000 Sq ft","answerDisplayText":"1000 - 2000 Sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200821,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"2000 - 3000 Sq ft","answerDisplayText":"2000 - 3000 Sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200823,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 3000 Sq ft","answerDisplayText":"More than 3000 Sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4007,"questionDisplayText":"Number of Stories","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many stories is your home?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10011,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10012,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2","answerDisplayText":"2","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10013,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"3","answerDisplayText":"3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":473,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"4 or more","answerDisplayText":"4 or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10011,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10012,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2","answerDisplayText":"2","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10013,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"3","answerDisplayText":"3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":473,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"4 or more","answerDisplayText":"4 or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}